

# Contact

Phone 46574564

Email edinanorge@gmail.com

Portfolio <u>edina-isztojka.netlify.com</u>

## Course

- JavaScript Course
  Udemy 2021
- Advance CSS and Sass Course
   Udemy 2021
- HTML CSS Course 2021
   Udemy 2021
- React Course 2023
   Udemy 2022

# Skill

- HTML 5
- CSS/ SASS
- JavaScript
- React
- Typescript
- Figma/Adobe XD

# Language

English

Norsk

Hungarian

# Edina Isztojka

# Front-end developer

As a recent graduate in Front-End Development, I am enthusiastic about developing user-friendly digital experiences. I'm always happy to learn new skills and stay updated with the latest trends in the field. I am excited to bring a positive and collaborative approach to any project and am ready to contribute to dynamic development teams.

# **Education**

2022 - 2024 Front-end development

Noroff-School of technology and digital media

Higher Professional Degree

2007 - 2010 **Department of Social Science** 

Sapientia Hungarian University

Bachelor Degree

2003 - 2007 Mathematics and IT

Kos Karoly high school

# **Work Experience**

**Q** 2024 - present

Skaun kommune

## Kindergarten child care

- Taking part in creating a secure and inclusive space where all children can develop, learn, and feel valued
- Maintaining daily child care involves activities such as changing diapers and feeding..

## 2024 - present

Upwork

#### Front end developer - freelencer

- Actively seeking diverse freelance projects to broaden experience and expertise.
- Specializing in tailored solutions by understanding and addressing individual client needs
- Scheduling and organizing tasks to ensure timely and successful project completion.

#### 2019 - 2022

## Full time mother

- Managing budgets, groceries, and domestic tasks while coordinating family schedules.
- Nurturing children and overseeing family activities for a balanced household.

#### 2014 - 2019

ISS AS.

## Hotel housekeeping

- Diligently cleaning and tidying up hotel rooms to maintain high standards of cleanliness, ensuring a positive and welcoming guest experience.
- Engaging in effective communication with hotel guests to understand and fulfill their specific needs

### 2017

Uloba - Independent living Norge AS.

### **Personal Assistant**

• Offering a helping hand to individuals with special needs by assisting with daily tasks, mobility, and personal care needs to enhance their quality of life.